Hello hello friends my name is Himanshu at this
time and I will keep bringing new videos for
this insurance custom map from my page and SIM ki my father three layer
which are
very useful for your family and friends if you like then
like and share and
subscribe my channel and don't forget to comment
today I am going to tell you about the
product which is a
fantastic fabulous product whose name
is
so let's start now first of all we will
talk about the
beautiful benefits of this policy only the first point
is Hi Sum Assured
hello in Hi Sum Insured we have three
sum assureds available such as swine
flu
and one crore packing point our entries in
which there is no upper age limit third
point is our hospitalization
expenses room rent and ICU recharges there is no
sub-limit
that in patient hospitalization and day
treatment now tools will be mentioned
and Priyanka's hospitalization is in the
30-day test and 60s will be respectfully
that fourth point is this  You will get our ambulance cover as per the
time limit or
when you give the original reset amount to the
company. Fifth point is
our organ donor cover which you will get as per the sum assured.
Sixth point is
automatic recharge which you
can also call restore benefit.
In this, if your Idea basement gets used up, then
hundred percent refill will be free of
charge. Seventh point is our no
claim bonus and no claim bonus. In super no
claim bonus, you will get ten percent every year.
Now two fifty percent
no claim bonus. On top of this, you will get 50% of this
every year. Now
2108.
Meanwhile, on top, you have additional premium
application.
In the eighth point, coverage comes for
modern treatment. In this, robotic surgery is included. Now someone should include
98. Our chronic disease includes
kidney, acid cover. Different
husband,
this plan has many benefits,
so let us talk about option constipation,
such as claim Shukla influential and don't see all that
this is the text of the shade of all the seats.  Clean Shaven
Protector: Your non-tribal items will be available in this.
Now the sum is insured.
Talking about the inflation shield,
consumer price inflation linking will be done, due
to which your sum insured will increase.
I said talking about
bonus,
if you have
used one of the objects of man should have used, then there will be no
impact on it. Let us
now talk about the policy terms. The minimum
sum insured in your policy terms is Rs.
125, Rs. 50 and Rs. 1 crore. There is no
limit in the minimum insurance. The
policy type is individual and family
floater. The
waiting period is 30 days.
In the pre-existing waiting period, positive
individuals have and existing deaths are
14178.
So let us now talk about the exclusions. The
exclusions include any suicide
attempt, drug abuse, use and misuse,
admission for primary lift, diagnostic
and evaluation purposes,
external congenital diseases.  And
things like gender treatment are excluded.
Thank you for watching my YouTube video.
If you like it, please subscribe to my YouTube
channel and check out more videos. I hope you
love me.